hey what's up everybody hope you're
doing well welcome to my YouTube channel
got a little bit of a throat thing going
on so remind my uh voice just a little
bit I'm excited on this channel I help
coaches mentors and trainers to scale
their businesses online and I want to
talk about lead generation getting leads
is the number one thing that you need to
do if you are a coach Mentor trainer and
it's the number one thing that
determines your ability to make the kind
of money that you want to make in fact
for every thousand leads that you have
you should be able to make six figures
with that that's an incredible statistic
because most people don't have even more
than a 100 leads and it's actually very
easy to get a th in fact just this last
week we generated over 150 New Leads
just doing a test with a small budget
less than $50 a day with Instagram ads
to be able to do that and I have a brand
new training right now that's up all
about Instagram ads you go check that
out it should be the link in the
description below if we're not working
on a different uh training right now but
I'd recommend that that you do check it
out it's this training right here that
I've actually put together for you 45
minute for 42 minute instant Instagram
ads class how we turn simple lowcost $10
a day Instagram ads into a sfig coaching
business without needing massive Tech
skills big budgets or burnout very
simple time to grow your profits not
your expenses now I want to talk about
lead generation because honestly it's
the most important thing that you can do
and the reason why is because nowadays
people don't buy from you they don't
become your client simply because you
have a great program or you have a great
product or a great course they buy it
from you because they trust that it's
going to get them something that there
is a means to an end that they're going
to get out of it have you ever looked
online for something that you wanted to
learn the only reason why you watch it
why you consume it is because it's a
means to an end even watching YouTube
videos like this are a means to an end
and so in your
business with your course or your
coaching program
is people see it as a means to an end
some way to get a result something that
they crave something that they they
desire more than anything else so you
have your program people are going to
buy it if they believe it's going to get
them something that they want or that
they desire your lead generation is what
attracts those people from social media
from YouTube from podcasts from JV joint
venture Partners into your ecosystem so
people people don't know who you are
starting out they have no clue they've
never heard of you and how many of you
are not willing usually to buy something
or do business with people that you've
never met before most people aren't and
and so you got to people got to spend
some time with you to get to know you if
they're going to want to make that
investment with you no matter how good
what you offer is there's not a a stage
that you're going to get to where you
you you're so good that people are just
going to buy from you just because
you're so good trust me I know I've been
in this for 20 22 years I think my
stuff's the best stuff that's out there
my coaching program is the best program
that's out there on lead generation
getting clients and yet I can't expect
just everybody to become my client would
I love it sure it'd be great but what I
do is I have to generate leads get
people into my ecosystem following what
I'm saying and then build trust with
those people to become my client so
there's a process of building trust and
the trust begins even before you
generate the leads so when we are
generating leads we have to use new
strategies the ways that we did them
years ago and I'm and I'm thinking even
three years ago the way that we
generated leads it doesn't work anymore
and that's the crazy part about it is is
that like if you follow have been
following me for a long time maybe you
learned how I taught three years ago
even a year and a half ago doesn't work
anymore and so there's brand new
strategies that I'm going to be breaking
down step by step in this video where
I'm going to walk you through that
process the the problem is this in the
lead generation that the digital
landscape has shifted so much towards
bite-sized content and people's
attention span is so low and they're
also in such a state
of problems agitation needing to solve
problems issues I saw a post the other
day that people go in Cycles we have
either have a thriving cycle or we have
a problem mitigation cycle right now we
are in the problem mitigation cycle is
what it is a couple years ago I think we
were in more of that thriving cycle
where you could just be like oh look at
all this great stuff that we've done now
it's like okay how do we mitigate the
issues of what's not working and we're
going to shift it's going going to go
right back into the thriving cycle very
soon so we got to pay attention to what
is the marketplace as a whole thinking
of a lot of that goes into
macroeconomics as well what's going on
in the greater economy as a whole is a
big part of it and so to generate leads
we got to honor all of these things we
got to honor the platforms that are out
there we got to honor the ways that
people interact people interact
differently online than they ever have
in fact a lot of people are reading more
than anything else and so there's
actually two forms of lead magnets more
than anything else that we are finding
are working the best number one is
ebooks number two is short form video
trainings something that's less than 45
minutes long it's not a long long form
webinar it's not a challenge it's not an
event but it's something that's 30 to 45
minutes long that people opt into to
solve a specific problem for them as I
showed you at the beginning of this
training that Instagram ads class that I
put together it's 42 minutes long solves
a real big problem right here about
running ads to get clients and again I'd
highly recommend you go check it out as
well ebooks are a great thing that's
generating a lot of leads for people you
can use artificial intelligence to build
out your lead lead books we all your
your your your lead books yeah that's
actually a great name to call it your
lead magnets and ebooks with that so
what we're doing right now is we're
using Evergreen lead magnets ebooks and
Evergreen short form video classes
people can watch something very simple
very quick that they can get access to
to join our email list and we are seeing
like wildfire the number of clients that
we're getting directly proportionate to
how much we're spending on ads is almost
200% higher than what we were getting
even 2 years ago doing Live Events and
challenges and that's the crazy part
about it now here's the thing I think
Live Events and challenges have a great
place but people get burnt out with them
so here's the strategy that I like to do
when it comes to that number one you
have your
ebooks or you have your short form video
right here okay and this is going to go
over to your email list now this is
going to get you a lot of clients but
for anybody who does not become a client
that is already on your email list after
somebody signs up for this this is
considered offer number one okay offer
number one is the first offer that
people see with you it solves some kind
of a problem that people have and you
can use artificial intelligence to
figure out what are those problems that
you can solve it's one of the best
brainstorming tools that you can use and
AI has only gotten that much better even
in just the last 30 days some of the
latest tools with artificial intell
elligence at the time of this recording
grock 3's thinking mode deep seek R1 uh
GPT
4.5 and uh Claude Sonet 3.7 these are
some of my favorites that we're using 03
mini these are incredible AI tools AI
algorithms that you can have access to
that you can get that can help you with
brainstorming coming up with great ideas
for your lead magnets now you'll get a
lot of sales this way but let's say
people don't become your client through
this what do you do well that's where
you nurture them you can send other
pieces of content like YouTube videos
like this you can send additional offers
let's say people don't become a client
of mine after watching my Instagram ads
class I got another class I'm making all
about Evergreen Marketing in about a
month and so let's say that we're going
to do that maybe every quarter we might
throw in a live event or a challenge to
mix it up to give people a little bit of
immersion that way it's a new way of
doing challenges that I like where you
do it again pre-recorded all the
sessions live and you have one final day
that's a live Q&A and I think that
that's actually really cool because it
gives people an opportunity to talk with
you live without you experiencing the
burnout that you would from having to
show up live every day in your challenge
it's like a win-win win for everybody if
you do it that way and that's one of the
new ways that we're starting to do
things that way one of the number one
things that I do in my business
everything is automated nothing that I
do it has to be like on the FL
except for my live coaching if I'm
coaching my clients live I will be in
there in our live sessions inside of my
wealthy coach Academy program now the
ways that we're getting clients and the
ways that we're actually generating
these leads is like this when I share
this approach that I'm about to share
with you with my client Ian Carroll he
was able to make over $40,000 a month in
his coaching business I shared this with
my client Don and she was able to bring
in $35,000 a month one of my client
Sandy she was able to bring in over
$20,000 a month in a brand new Niche
within 30 days of trying these
strategies and What's the Difference
Maker behind this it's about
implementing the Evergreen marketing
strategy so what you got to do is this
as you figure
out what is the number
one
desire that somebody has that is
connected to your framework okay so you
have a framework in your business if
you're a coach if you're a mentor if
you're a trainer what is the number one
desire that people who can use your
framework want again this is where we
use AI to help us brainstorm this but I
would like you to take your own brain
and think about this as well is what is
the thing that a person who could use
your framework of your coaching every
coaching program every course has a
framework a system a methodology that it
is now I want you to think about the
person who's doing that what is their
desire and it goes goes beyond just what
you teach or coach on it goes much
deeper into what is the life that
they're creating what is the journey
that they're on the heroes Journey that
they're on and if you've never heard
about the hero's journey before the
hero's journey is made popular through
Joseph Campbell's uh monom myth is what
this is a part of Joseph Campbell's the
hero's journey uh breaks this down for
us but inside of every single Marketing
System every single coaching program it
really is the hero's journey and this is
the biggest part about it the hero's
journey is people start in a place right
here I'm going to zoom in called The
Ordinary World and then they meet the
mentor a supernatural Aid before they go
into tests and trials and this is where
you are that helps people and you help
them completely transform their life
from The Ordinary World into the Special
World the special world is your coaching
program where they go through this
transformation and they come out
resurrected with new skills to go along
the journey and to go onto that hero's
journey and become a hero so you as a
coach as a mentor as a course creator
are taking people through that hero's
journey every single time they join your
ecosystem every single time that they're
becoming a lead of yours that's
connected to their desires then what you
do is you put that into either an ebook
or some kind of a
pre-recorded training that's on video I
just use Vimeo I keep it very simple
Vimeo link on a page people sign up for
it I send them an email autoresponder
with the link to it and then from there
I'm able to tell people about my
framework my system I give them some
strategies some insights and then
ultimately they learn about my coaching
program and my mentorship program and
that my friends is the blueprint that we
use on repeat constantly in our business
every single thing that we do in our
business all roads lead to our lead
magnet which then all lead magnets lead
to our coaching program and again listen
I'd love to see you as a part of that
coaching program inside of my wealthy
coach Academy program where I work with
you come alongside you personally to
guide you and direct you through
developing your landing pages coming up
with your ads your sales copy what do
you say how do you say it how do you
close more sales how do you get this
stuff actually working for you so I'd
love to see you in there jump in there
with us when you have a chance to do so
and make sure to subscribe to this page
to get more strategies on what's working
right now this is what's working to
generate leads you figure out what
people desire you package it as
something an ebook or a video training
and then you put that out there and you
can then Market it to people we Market
it through simple Instagram ads it's one
of the best ways that we do it very
simple low Tech low cost and that's what
generates leads all right I'll see you
in our next video and we will talk soon
have a good one